http://www.stirlingcryogenics.eu/en/cookies-and-privacy

Toggle navigation
HomeProductsCryocoolersLiquid Nitrogen Production SystemsLNG Liquefying SystemsCustom (Closed Loop) Cooling SystemsLiquid Air Production SystemsLiquid Oxygen Production SystemsMarketsAerospaceBiostorageFood & BeverageHealthcareLNG & BiogasMaritimeResearchHTSUniversitiesIndustryProjectsAerospaceBiostorageFood & BeverageHealthcareLNG & BiogasMaritimeResearchHTSUniversitiesEntertainmentThe Stirling CycleEventsNewsDocumentsAbout usContact
Cookies and Privacy
Cookie and Privacy Declaration Stirling Cryogenics B.V.
Stirling Cryogenics is aware that you have confidence in us. We see it as our responsibility to protect your privacy. This document is designed to inform you about what details we collect when you use our website, why we collect it and how this helps us to improve your user experience. So then you understand exactly how we work.
This page was last modified on 08-01-2019
1. Privacy declaration
Stirling Cryogenics processes personal data from you because you make use of our services. Stirling Cryogenics respects the privacy of all users of its site and ensures that the personal information you give us will be treated confidentially.
Below an overview of the personal data that we process:
First and last name
Phone number
E-mail address
Company
Country, City
Special and/or sensitive personal data that we process
Our website and/or services do not intend to collect data from website visitors who are under 16 years old. Unless they have permission from a parent or guardian. However, we cannot check if a visitor is older than 16. We also recommend parents to be involved in the online activities of their children, in order to prevent any data being collected about children without parental consent
Purposes
When you sign up for one of our services or fill in a contact or registration form on the website, we ask you to provide personal information. This data is used to be able to carry out services. The data is stored in the servers of Stirling Cryogenics or those of a third party.
We process your personal information for the following purposes:
To inform you about changes to our services. And to be able to call you, if necessary, to carry out our services.
Sending our newsletter
We do not collect or use information for purposes other than the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, unless we have obtained your approval in advance.
Choices for personal information
We offer all visitors the opportunity to view, change, or delete all personal information provided to us at any time. If you want to change your data or you want to remove yourself from our files, please contact us. We will as soon as possible, no later than four weeks to respond to your request. See below for contact information.
Edit/unsubscribe newsletter service
At the bottom of each newsletter you will find the option to unsubscribe.
Security
Stirling Cryogenics takes the protection of your data seriously and adopts all appropriate measures to prevent abuse, loss, unauthorized access, unwanted disclosure and unauthorized modification.
Questions and feedback
We regularly review our compliance with this Privacy Policy. If you have questions about this privacy statement, please contact us:
Stirling Cryogenics B.V.Science Park Eindhoven 50035692 EB Son, Netherlands
+31 40 2677 300info@stirlingcryogenics.eu
2. Cookie declaration
Outline of website visit
The website www.stirlingcryogenics.eu (Stirling Cryogenics B.V., Chamber of Commerce: 73238783) uses functional, analytic and tracking cookies. A cookie is a small text file stored on the first visit to this website by your browser on your hard drive of your computer. The information stored therein can be sent back to our servers when you visit again.
First-party cookies
First-party cookies are cookie files that are sent from this website and will not be shared with third parties. We use first-party cookies, among other things to ensure that you have a better website experience, they are also called functional cookies. First-party cookies cannot identify you personally, cookies do not know who you are (name), what your address or e-mail address is.
Functional purposes
Examples of cookies used for functional purposes on www.stirlingcryogenics.eu
Session cookies help us see which parts of the site you viewed during your website visit. This enables us to adapt our services as much as possible to the surfing habits of our visitors. These cookies are automatically deleted when you close your web browser.
User input cookies, remember user actions on a website. An example of this is remembering shopping basket items.
User interface customization cookies are used to remember your preferences. An example of this is a language preference.
Cookie Notification cookie; remembers whether you agree with cookies or if you have clicked the cookie banner away.
Analytical purposes
Analytical cookies are also first party cookies. These cookies measure how many people visit the website or which pages function well or poorly. This gives us insights that help us to improve the website for you.
Google Analytics
This tool gives an insight into understanding for example how visitors came to the site, which pages visitors have looked at and how much time visitors spend on average on the website.
Third-party cookies; where we ask for your permission
We use cookies to track your surfing habits so that we can offer customized content and advertising. On www.stirlingcryogenics.eu cookies are also posted by third parties. These include cookies from advertisers and/or social media. Here is an overview of the third-party cookies we use, why they are used and, if possible, what data they collect.
Remarketing
A remarketing cookie keeps track of products or pages you view or can track whether you've made a purchase/request in response to one of our ads. This information is very valuable to us; in this way we can measure the success of our marketing campaigns and how well our offering connects to our target audience.
This cookie file can also ensure that our ads are matched to third party websites based upon your interests, page views or are provided with interesting offers. This cookie file cannot identify you personally, the cookie does not know who you are (name), what your address or e-mail address is.
This cookie file is put on www.stirlingcryogenics.eu by the following parties:
Google AdWords
Google Analytics
Doubleclick
Google Analytics  (Extended)
Google Analytics is used in addition to the analytical aspect to be able to provide you interesting offers and advertisements. This cookie file stores, based on your IP address, for example, what products you are viewing. So we can show relevant ads or content on other websites. The cookie cannot identify you personally, the cookie does not know who you are (name), what your address or email address is. Your IP data and statistics are anonymous to us, we cannot see how often individual visitors visit, what pages they go through and other operations they perform. For this Analytics cookie you give consent.
The Analytics cookie, previously called Analytical (first-party) cookies, does not collect any information that we could personally approach you with. This cookie does not require any consent.
Social media cookies
For the specific cookies that social media company’s use and how they collect these data, we refer you to the statements of the parties concerned. The following cookies are placed on the website through social media.
Facebook plugin
This cookie allows you to instantly like or share an article from the website.
This cookie keeps track of the products you are viewing. So this product can be later shown in relevant ads.
Twitter plugin
This cookie allows you to instantly share an article from the website.
This cookie keeps track of the products you are viewing. So this product can be later shown in relevant ads.
LinkedIn plugin
This cookie allows you to instantly share an article from the website.
Youtube plugin
This cookie allows you to instantly share a video from the website.
Google+ plugin
This cookie allows you to instantly share an article from the website.
Remove and refuse cookies
You have the right to refuse cookies. Upon entering the www.stirlingcryogenics.eu we will give you this opportunity. Have you accepted cookies in the past? Then you won’t get this question again from us. This is already stored for your convenience.
Do you want to remove cookies or disable them? That is possible via your browser settings. Please note that then some of the website functionality will no longer work properly.
Sitemap
HomeProductsCryocoolersLiquid Nitrogen Production SystemsLNG Liquefying SystemsCustom (Closed Loop) Cooling SystemsLiquid Air Production SystemsLiquid Oxygen Production SystemsMarketsAerospaceBiostorageFood & BeverageHealthcareLNG & BiogasMaritimeResearchHTSUniversitiesIndustryProjectsAerospaceBiostorageFood & BeverageHealthcareLNG & BiogasMaritimeResearchHTSUniversitiesEntertainmentThe Stirling CycleEventsNewsDocumentsAbout usContactCookies and PrivacyDisclaimer
Website by Sprite IT
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. Read more about our Cookie Policy.
